<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>noboru.top</title>
  <link href="https://noboru.top/"/>
  <link href="https://www.noboru.top/blog/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <id>https://noboru.top/</id>
  <updated>2024-12-12T03:00:00Z</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Muze Lyu</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>Why and How I create my first blog</title>
    <link href="https://www.noboru.top/blog/why-and-how-I-create-my-first-blog.html"/>
    <id>https://www.noboru.top/blog/why-and-how-I-create-my-first-blog.html</id>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[         
        <h2>Why</h2>
        <p>Graduation is around the corner, implying the end of the first chapter of my life. The wind of December passes through my and carries away all the words that I have not dared to say or have yet to findd the meaning to say. Though the road ahead remains foggy, I believe it's time to either embark on a new journey or watch everything rot for the rest of my life.</p>
        <h2>How</h2>
        <p>For personal preference, GitHub Pages with plain HTML and CSS is more than sufficient, the document is well-written and easy to follow, which leads to a quite smooth experience. GPT-4o mini did most of the coding for me, and with minimal prompt, the generated color theme and layout was basically all I wanted, requiring only a few minor adjustment.</p>
        <p>The only frustration I faced was when I tried to add my LinkedIn account, the accout got restricted after login and I was told to upload my ID to recover. I haven't posted anything since registering and the only things that could be wrong were my IP address and browser extensions. It's so difficult to understand the point behind LinkedIn's anti-spam policy.</p>
        <h2>Next</h2>
        <p>1. Automate the process of converting Markdown to HTML, updating archive list and atom file.</p>
        <p>2. Add support for mobile device with small display.</p>
      ]]>
    </content>
    <published>2024-12-12T02:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2024-12-12T03:00:00Z</updated>
  </entry>
</feed>
